[Disclaimer: All depicted events are fictional
[Descargo de responsabilidad: Todos los eventos representados son ficticios.]
(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
(Ver en www.kisskh.xyz Administrador de soporte)
and for entertainment purposes only; viewer discretion is advised]
y únicamente con fines de entretenimiento; se recomienda discreción al espectador.
How many cups of coffee did you have?
¿Cuántas tazas de café tomaste?
Do you know any limits?
¿Conoces algún límite?
Just stop being so cute.
Deja de ser tan lindo.
Don't ever push through it again, alright?
No vuelvas a forzarlo nunca más, ¿de acuerdo?
I'm worried about you.
Estoy preocupado por ti.
Did you just take me to your house?
¿Acabas de llevarme a tu casa?
I brought Duang with me today.
Hoy traje a Duang conmigo.
Answer me.
Respóndeme.
Will you be my boyfriend, Duang?
¿Quieres ser mi novio, Duang?
Of course, I will.
Por supuesto que sí.
Through every chapter,
A través de cada capítulo,
it's always gonna be you, Qin.
Siempre serás tú, Qin.
It's always gonna be you, Duang.
Siempre serás tú, Duang.
I love you.
Te amo.
What are you looking at, good boy?
¿Qué miras, buen chico?
I love you, too.
Yo también te amo.
Hm?
¿Eh?
It's a shame
Es una pena
that I didn't get to meet you back in high school.
Lamento no haberte conocido en la escuela secundaria.
What would you do if you did?
¿Qué harías si lo hicieras?
I would've hit on you back then.
Te habría tirado los tejos en aquel entonces.
If we had started dating back then,
Si hubiéramos empezado a salir en aquel entonces,
we might have broken up.
Podríamos haber roto.
Impossible.
Imposible.
I'd never break up with you.
Jamás rompería contigo.
You can't break up on your own either.
Tampoco puedes romper la relación por tu cuenta.
No, let's not talk about this.
No, no hablemos de esto.
I thank you for choosing me.
Le agradezco que me haya elegido.
It's because we choose each other, Duang.
Es porque nos elegimos el uno al otro, Duang.
From now on, I'll devote my love to you even more.
De ahora en adelante, te dedicaré mi amor aún más.
Listen.
Escuchar.
I'll also love you even more.
Yo también te amaré aún más.
I'm starving.
Estoy hambriento.
What time is this?
¿Qué hora es?
It's 2 A.M.
Son las 2 de la madrugada.
Making this cute face...
Haciendo esta carita tan linda...
You want stir-fried shrimp with garlic?
¿Quieres gambas salteadas con ajo?
You know me too well.
Me conoces demasiado bien.
Well...
Bien...
We'll go to the restaurant when you're free.
Iremos al restaurante cuando estés libre.
For now, let's have instant noodles.
Por ahora, comamos fideos instantáneos.
I'll make them for you.
Te las haré.
You're spoiling me again.
Me estás malcriando otra vez.
Only with you.
Solo contigo.
[Duang With You]
[Duang contigo]
♫I'm not leaving soon, so bear with me♫
♫No me iré pronto, así que tengan paciencia conmigo♫
♫Wherever you are is where I'll always be♫
♫Dondequiera que estés, allí estaré siempre♫
♫Wherever you go, I'll find you eventually♫
♫Dondequiera que vayas, te encontraré tarde o temprano♫
♫You may push me away, but I won't flee♫
♫Puedes alejarme, pero no huiré♫
♫Who would you love if it weren't me?♫
♫¿A quién amarías si no fuera a mí?♫
♫So, wanna make a deal, maybe?♫
♫¿Entonces, quieres hacer un trato, tal vez?♫
♫Alright, alright, don't worry♫
♫Vale, vale, no te preocupes♫
♫Just date me first, take it easy♫
♫Solo sal conmigo primero, tómalo con calma♫
♫I'll be so cute you'll fall naturally♫
♫Seré tan linda que te enamorarás naturalmente♫
♫No matter what, you'll always run into me♫
♫Pase lo que pase, siempre te toparás conmigo♫
♫Okay, okay, let it be♫
♫Vale, vale, que así sea♫
♫I know you're also into me,♫
♫Sé que tú también estás interesado en mí,♫
♫Don't you feel the same? I can see♫
♫¿No sientes lo mismo? Puedo verlo♫
♫I'll keep on flirting, don't try to avoid me♫
♫Seguiré coqueteando, no intentes evitarme♫
♫'Cause I won't stop till you fall for me♫
♫Porque no pararé hasta que te enamores de mí♫
♫I'll keep on flirting, I won't stop, I guarantee♫
♫Seguiré coqueteando, no pararé, te lo garantizo♫
♫I'll love you hard, and once you say yes, I'll set you free♫
♫Te amaré con intensidad, y una vez que digas que sí, te dejaré libre♫
[Duang With You]
[Duang contigo]
Hurry up,
Apresúrate,
so I can take a shower.
para poder ducharme.
You can take a shower now. I'm fine.
Ya puedes ducharte. Estoy bien.
You are, but I'm not.
Tú sí, pero yo no.
Quickly.
Rápidamente.
Hurry up,
Apresúrate,
then you can shower right after me.
Entonces podrás ducharte justo después de mí.
You can take your time.
Puedes tomarte tu tiempo.
You've got no classes today.
Hoy no tienes clases.
I do, but I can be late.
Sí, pero a veces llego tarde.
It's fine.
Está bien.
You can't be late.
No puedes llegar tarde.
I'm coming with you.
Voy contigo.
Huh?
¿Eh?
Why are you surprised?
¿Por qué te sorprende?
It's just me hanging out in class with you.
Solo estoy pasando el rato contigo en clase.
Ow!
¡Ay!
Do you really have to be this excited?
¿De verdad tienes que estar tan emocionado?
You don't get it.
No lo entiendes.
Are you trying to kill me?
¿Estás intentando matarme?
Stop saying that.
Deja de decir eso.
If you die, I'll get myself a new lover.
Si mueres, me buscaré un nuevo amante.
You can't!
¡No puedes!
I don't want that to happen.
No quiero que eso suceda.
Get out already.
¡Fuera de aquí ya!
I'm taking a shower.
Me estoy duchando.
Okay.
Bueno.
I'll leave now.
Me voy ahora.
I'm not going to die anytime soon, either.
Yo tampoco voy a morir pronto.
You can only have me as your sweetheart, alright?
Solo puedes tenerme a mí como tu amorcito, ¿entendido?
I know.
Lo sé.
You can't be with anyone else either.
Tú tampoco puedes estar con nadie más.
Now, get out.
Ahora, lárgate.
Fit check. Fit check.
Comprobación de ajuste. Comprobación de ajuste.
Your shirt actually fits.
Tu camisa te queda bien.
One second...
Un segundo...
I love this fragrance when it's on you.
Me encanta esta fragancia cuando la llevas puesta.
We're wearing the same one.
Llevamos la misma.
Let's take a selfie.
Vamos a tomarnos una selfie.
Why do you want to take selfies?
¿Por qué quieres tomarte selfies?
Just take a look.
Solo echa un vistazo.
What's the matter,
Qué pasa,
huh?
¿eh?
I'm fine.
Estoy bien.
What's wrong?
¿Qué ocurre?
Huh?
¿Eh?
I can tell something's wrong.
Puedo notar que algo anda mal.
What's wrong?
¿Qué ocurre?
Don't tease me.
No me tomes el pelo.
I'm not teasing you.
No te estoy tomando el pelo.
Why are you turning away from me?
¿Por qué te alejas de mí?
Aww...
Oooh...
It's okay. Don't cry.
Está bien. No llores.
Let me get myself ready first,
Déjame prepararme primero,
or you'll be late.
o llegarás tarde.
So he finally made it official on Close Friends?
¿Así que finalmente lo hizo oficial en Close Friends?
Well, you're like a caretaker prime minister.
Bueno, eres como un primer ministro interino.
Even though you take the position, nobody counts it.
Aunque ocupes el puesto, nadie lo tiene en cuenta.
You guys are so jealous! You meanie!
¡Qué celosos están! ¡Qué malos!
Can we go now?
¿Podemos irnos ya?
Alright. Let's go.
Muy bien. Vamos.
- Hey! - Whoa!
- ¡Oye! - ¡Guau!
What's the tagged selfie on Instagram about?
¿De qué trata la selfie etiquetada en Instagram?
"I'm all yours."
"Soy todo tuyo."
Seriously?
¿En serio?
Did you steal his phone to post it?
¿Le robaste el teléfono para publicarlo?
He didn't. I typed it myself.
No lo hizo. Lo escribí yo mismo.
- Huh?! - Huh?
- ¡¿Eh?! - ¿Eh?
Do you want more snacks?
¿Quieres más aperitivos?
I'll get them before the professor calls the roll.
Las conseguiré antes de que el profesor pase lista.
Well, shall we head inside?
Bueno, ¿entramos?
Can we sit in the back?
¿Podemos sentarnos atrás?
Sure thing.
Claro que sí.
Qin is talking as if he's going to be in our class.
Qin habla como si fuera a estar en nuestra clase.
Yeah.
Sí.
Mm.
Mm.
Is the professor strict?
¿Es estricto el profesor?
- Huh?! - Huh?
- ¡¿Eh?! - ¿Eh?
Why the hell are you guys surprised?
¿Por qué diablos están sorprendidos?
Your shirt looks a bit tight, no?
Tu camisa te queda un poco ajustada, ¿no?
Switching up your look?
¿Quieres cambiar de look?
Yeah.
Sí.
Well...
Bien...
I'm wearing his shirt.
Llevo puesta su camisa.
What's weird about wearing my boyfriend's clothes?
¿Qué tiene de raro usar la ropa de mi novio?
- Huh?! - Huh?
- ¡¿Eh?! - ¿Eh?
I
I
and Qin
y Qin
are now boyfriends.
Ahora son novios.
What did you say?
¿Qué dijiste?
That made me get up from my seat.
Eso me hizo levantarme de mi asiento.
So?
¿Entonces?
Want me to repeat that?
¿Quieres que lo repita?
I
I
and Qin
y Qin
are boyfriends now.
ahora son novios.
Qin...
Qin...
I'm so sorry.
Lo siento mucho.
- What do you mean by that? - Ow!
- ¿Qué quieres decir con eso? - ¡Ay!
I was just kidding.
Solo estaba bromeando.
Congratulations.
Felicidades.
Took you forever.
Te ha llevado una eternidad.
How do single guys sit in class?
¿Cómo se sientan los chicos solteros en clase?
Because couples hug each other's arms while studying.
Porque las parejas se abrazan mientras estudian.
Hey! Can you be gentle?
¡Oye! ¿Puedes ser amable?
Here. Take a sip.
Toma. Bebe un sorbo.
Drink up.
Beberse todo.
Students,
Estudiantes,
when drawing a line,
al trazar una línea,
whether it's a curve, a straight line,
ya sea una curva, una línea recta,
or whatever the fuck it is,
o lo que sea,
how many times have I told you
¿Cuántas veces te lo he dicho?
not to draw it by hand?
¿No dibujarlo a mano?
Do you still want it?
¿Todavía lo quieres?
- One just arrived today. - Instead, what do we use to draw it?
- Acaba de llegar uno hoy. - ¿Y qué usamos para dibujarlo?
Feelings,
Sentimientos,
emotions,
emociones,
inspirations,
inspiraciones,
and life experiences.
y experiencias de vida.
I do. How much is it?
Sí. ¿Cuánto cuesta?
And what else?
¿Y qué más?
Tears.
Lágrimas.
- I'll pay immediately. - The tears you shed during a heartbreak.
- Pagaré inmediatamente. - Las lágrimas que derramas durante una ruptura amorosa.
Use your feelings.
Déjate guiar por tus sentimientos.
55,000 baht.
55.000 baht.
Express it through your lines.
Exprésalo a través de tus versos.
Put your soul into them.
Pon tu alma en ellos.
Pour...
Para...
Jamie!
¡Jamie!
Gosh, what is it, Professor?
¡Caramba! ¿Qué ocurre, profesor?
I was just resting my eyes.
Solo estaba descansando la vista.
How many years do you think I've been a professor?
¿Cuántos años crees que llevo siendo profesor?
Do you know how many students have used that excuse?
¿Sabes cuántos estudiantes han usado esa excusa?
Oh...
Oh...
Professor, have you ever heard of this:
Profesor, ¿ha oído hablar alguna vez de esto?
"Waking up looking too handsome, so back to sleep I go"?
"¿Me despierto luciendo demasiado guapo, así que vuelvo a dormirme?"
Never heard of that.
Nunca había oído hablar de eso.
Sounds like you pulled it out of your ass.
Parece que te lo has sacado del culo.
Right, right.
Claro, claro.
Who the hell are you?
¿Quién demonios eres?
You don't look familiar. Who are you?
No me resultas familiar. ¿Quién eres?
Uh...
Oh...
You said that
Dijiste eso
we have to draw with inspiration?
¿Tenemos que dibujar con inspiración?
That's why I brought my source of inspiration to class.
Por eso traje mi fuente de inspiración a clase.
Sheesh!
¡Caramba!
Yeah.
Sí.
Students, this is a great example.
Estudiantes, este es un gran ejemplo.
- Your inspiration? - Yes.
- ¿Tu inspiración? - Sí.
I don't mind that.
No me importa.
Just make sure he doesn't disturb the other students.
Solo asegúrate de que no moleste a los demás estudiantes.
Students.
Estudiantes.
Lines are very important.
Las líneas son muy importantes.
Today, we're drawing a still life,
Hoy vamos a dibujar una naturaleza muerta,
turning an inanimate object into something lively.
convertir un objeto inanimado en algo animado.
Thus, for straight lines,
Por lo tanto, para líneas rectas,
use a protractor to draw the angles.
Utiliza un transportador para dibujar los ángulos.
How would that create a straight line?
¿Cómo se podría crear una línea recta con eso?
There, look at the curves and the shadow.
Ahí, fíjate en las curvas y la sombra.
Ow...
Ay...
I'm freaking tired.
Estoy agotada.
Are you coming with me?
¿Vienes conmigo?
Are you free?
¿Estás libre?
You, seriously...
¿En serio tú...?
Why did you force Qin to sit through class with you?
¿Por qué obligaste a Qin a quedarse en clase contigo?
He wasn't having a tough time here.
No lo estaba pasando mal aquí.
I chose to come here,
Elegí venir aquí,
so we could have stir-fried garlic shrimp sooner.
para que pudiéramos tener gambas salteadas con ajo antes.
That's true.
Eso es cierto.
Let's go eat it, shall we?
Vamos a comerlo, ¿de acuerdo?
- Oh, sorry. - Let's go.
- Oh, lo siento. - Vámonos.
No care for his friends, whatsoever.
No le importaban en absoluto sus amigos.
I feel like I've been there with him throughout his love journey.
Siento que he estado a su lado durante toda su historia de amor.
Since Day 0,
Desde el día 0,
it's been the two of us.
Hemos sido nosotros dos.
Shall we pull his legs?
¿Le tomamos el pelo?
Let's go after him.
Vamos a por él.
What's the hurry, buddy?
¿Cuál es la prisa, amigo?
You're ditching us now that you've got Qin?
¿ Nos estás abandonando ahora que tienes a Qin?
Who are you guys?
¿Quiénes sois vosotros?
I've never met you two.
Nunca los he conocido.
Fine, Duang.
Bien, Duang.
You asked for this.
Tú lo pediste.
- Move, Qin. - Oh?
- Muévete, Qin. - ¿Ah?
- Please move, Qin. - Oh?!
- Por favor, muévete, Qin. - ¡¿Oh?!
- Ha! - Ow!
- Ha! - Ow!
- Let go! - Pae, ready?
- ¡Suéltalo! - Pae, ¿listo?
Don't!
¡No!
One...
Uno...
Two...
Dos...
Three...
Tres...
I'm taking Qin to get some stir-fried garlic shrimp!
¡Voy a llevar a Qin a comer gambas salteadas con ajo!
Would you like me to peel the shrimp for you, Qin?
¿Quieres que te pele los camarones, Qin?
So nosy, you guys.
¡Qué curiosos sois!
Qin, help me...
Qin, ayúdame...
Help me, please.
Ayúdame, por favor.
- Gosh! - Come on!
- ¡Caramba! - ¡Vamos!
- Get up by yourself. - Help yourself.
- Levántate por tu cuenta. - Sírvete tú mismo.
- Hey! - Ah!
- ¡Oye! - ¡Ah!
That's enough.
Ya es suficiente.
We're sending you flying this time.
Esta vez te vamos a mandar a volar.
- One... - Ah!
- Uno... - ¡Ah!
Two...
Dos...
Like the wind!
¡Como el viento!
Nothing is by chance.
Nada es casualidad.
Come on!
¡Vamos!
You're holding his hand a bit too tight, no?
Le estás apretando la mano un poco demasiado fuerte, ¿no?
You want to make that clear, don't you?
Quieres dejar eso claro, ¿verdad?
I'm the first puppy to be the captain.
Soy el primer cachorro en ser capitán.
The world must know this.
El mundo debe saber esto.
I'm so jealous of him.
¡Qué envidia me da!
- Yeah. - What captain?
- Sí. - ¿Qué capitán?
I want to tease him again.
Quiero volver a burlarme de él.
Let's.
Vamos.
Here you go.
Aquí tienes.
If you're not full, we can order more.
Si aún no está satisfecho, podemos pedir más.
It's a weekday, so why are there so many people?
Es un día laborable, ¿por qué hay tanta gente?
Hello!
¡Hola!
- Aha! - Oh?
- ¡Ajá! - ¿Oh?
Excuse me, plates for 4 people, please!
Disculpe, ¡platos para 4 personas, por favor!
Right! Coming right up.
¡Exacto! Enseguida.
How did you get here?
¿Cómo llegaste aquí?
- Here are your plates. - Thank you.
- Aquí están sus platos. - Gracias.
Not ordering anything else, aren't you?
No vas a pedir nada más, ¿verdad?
What the hell? Go and sit somewhere else!
¿Qué demonios? ¡ Vete a sentarte a otro sitio!
Shoo! Shoo!
¡Fuera! ¡Fuera!
Do you mind if we sit with you, Qin?
¿Te importa si nos sentamos contigo, Qin?
Go ahead.
Adelante.
You guys always ruin my moments.
Siempre me arruinan mis momentos.
This is my cue, alright?
Esta es mi señal, ¿de acuerdo?
Gosh.
Dios mío.
We don't have that many moments.
No tenemos tantos momentos.
You want to have it all by yourself?
¿Quieres tenerlo todo para ti solo?
Yeah.
Sí.
You're the biggest whiner and crybaby here,
Eres el mayor quejica y llorón aquí,
you lover boy of Nakhon Pathom.
tú, el chico enamorado de Nakhon Pathom.
You approached Qin through me,
Te acercaste a Qin a través de mí,
but now that you're dating, you chose to keep me in the dark.
Pero ahora que estás saliendo con alguien, has decidido mantenerme en la ignorancia.
I was about to tell you, but you've got no classes today.
Estaba a punto de decírtelo, pero hoy no tienes clases.
Duang, you're so lucky
Duang, tienes mucha suerte.
to have Qin as your sweetheart.
Tener a Qin como tu pareja.
Yeah, look at him.
Sí, míralo.
It's almost impossible to win his heart.
Es casi imposible ganarse su corazón.
You're so lucky that he says yes.
Tienes muchísima suerte de que diga que sí.
Ahem!
¡Ejem!
Allow me to speak up as the lover boy's best friend.
Permítanme hablar como el mejor amigo del chico enamorado.
Duang is such a great guy.
Duang es un tipo genial.
Saying no to him is a big mistake.
Decirle que no es un gran error.
Qin, you pulled a secret rare. Do you know why?
Qin, sacaste una carta rara secreta. ¿Sabes por qué?
He does everything for you,
Él hace todo por ti,
treating you like a princess.
Te trataré como a una princesa.
You're really lucky, Qin.
Tienes mucha suerte, Qin.
Duang is the best there is.
Duang es el mejor que existe.
I'd like to object.
Me gustaría objetar.
My friend Qin is the best.
Mi amigo Qin es el mejor.
He doesn't even care about the Communications Faculty King.
Ni siquiera le importa el rey de la facultad de comunicaciones.
Duang simply lucked out.
Duang simplemente tuvo suerte.
Yeah, and soon enough, Qin will become famous
Sí, y muy pronto Qin se hará famoso.
nationwide
a escala nacional
and globally.
y a nivel mundial.
This is luckier than hitting the jackpot.
Esto es tener más suerte que ganar el premio gordo.
- True! - Right?
- ¡Cierto! - ¿Verdad?
- Am I right? - I agreed with that one.
- ¿Tengo razón? - Estoy de acuerdo con eso.
Qin is the best.
Qin es el mejor.
- Stupid Duang!
- ¡Estúpido Duang!
I'm not going to call you "unique" anymore!
¡Ya no te voy a llamar "único"!
I'm going to call you "Stupid Duang"!
¡Te voy a llamar "Estúpido Duang"!
Yeah.
Sí.
Stupid Duang!
¡Estúpido Duang!
What the heck?
¿Qué demonios?
Alright. Dig in.
Muy bien. ¡A comer!
Come on.
Vamos.
Surprise!
¡Sorpresa!
For what?
¿Para qué?
Oh...
Oh...
You're not excited?
¿No estás emocionado?
Look what's inside.
Mira lo que hay dentro.
Why'd you get me this?
¿Por qué me compraste esto?
It's expensive.
Es caro.
Oh...
Oh...
Come on.
Vamos.
You're not delighted?
¿No estás encantado?
How much did you pay for it?
¿Cuánto pagaste por él?
50,000 baht?!
¡¿50.000 baht?!
Plus 5,000.
Más 5.000.
- Sell it. - What?
- Véndelo. - ¿Qué?
You want it, don't you?
Lo deseas, ¿verdad?
How much money do you have left?
¿Cuánto dinero te queda?
Mm...
Mm...
- A decent amount. - How much?
- Una cantidad decente. - ¿Cuánto?
Sell it, or else I'll be mad at you.
Véndelo, o me enfadaré contigo.
No! Listen to me first.
¡No! Escúchame primero.
It's true that it costs an arm and a leg,
Es cierto que cuesta un ojo de la cara,
but I really want to give it to you.
pero de verdad quiero dártelo.
It's not that I got it for you simply because you wanted it either.
Tampoco es que te lo haya comprado simplemente porque lo querías.
This film camera represents me.
Esta cámara de fotos me representa.
When you go out to take photos,
Cuando salgas a tomar fotos,
if I can't be there with you,
Si no puedo estar allí contigo,
it'll feel like I am.
Me sentiré como si lo fuera.
I appreciate that you care,
Aprecio que te preocupes,
but this is too expensive.
pero esto es demasiado caro.
It's not.
Que no es.
It's the first gift for our relationship.
Es el primer regalo de nuestra relación.
On top of that,
Además de eso,
I'm going to get you a monthiversary gift
Te voy a comprar un regalo de aniversario mensual
on the 16th of every month to celebrate the day we started dating.
El día 16 de cada mes para celebrar el día en que empezamos a salir.
Don't.
No.
Why buy me gifts every month?
¿Por qué me compran regalos todos los meses?
55,000 baht is just too expensive.
55.000 baht es demasiado caro.
Oh, it's not.
Oh, no lo es.
Your shoes cost even more.
Tus zapatos cuestan aún más.
This is nothing.
Esto no es nada.
Duang.
Plan.
Yes?
¿Sí?
I know.
Lo sé.
Return it.
Devuélvelo.
It's the first gift for our relationship, though.
Es el primer regalo de nuestra relación.
I do want to accept a gift from you,
Sí quiero aceptar un regalo de tu parte,
but I can't if it costs this much.
Pero no puedo si cuesta tanto.
I'm your boyfriend,
Soy tu novio,
and I want to be a good partner to you.
y quiero ser un buen compañero para ti.
You want me to accept a gift that costs you so much?
¿Quieres que acepte un regalo que te cuesta tanto?
I just can't.
Simplemente no puedo.
Contact the camera store and get a refund.
Contacta con la tienda de cámaras y solicita un reembolso.
Or sell it around Siam.
O venderlo por todo Siam.
They might buy it from you.
Podrían comprártelo a ti.
Understand?
¿Entender?
I understand.
Entiendo.
Does giving him flowers at the jazz showcase
¿Le dan flores en el espectáculo de jazz?
feel too simple?
¿Te parece demasiado simple?
What will you give him, then?
¿Qué le darás entonces?
A gift basket?
¿Una cesta de regalo?
How about balloons?
¿Qué tal globos?
How about wearing a mascot suit?
¿Qué tal si te pones un disfraz de mascota?
That'd be lovely.
Eso sería estupendo.
If you want to go overboard,
Si quieres exagerar,
hire a sound truck for the showcase.
Contratar un camión de sonido para la presentación.
A sound truck, my ass!
¡Un camión de sonido, ni hablar!
No need to be sarcastic.
No hay necesidad de ser sarcástico.
Good on you for knowing I was being sarcastic.
Bien por ti por darte cuenta de que estaba siendo sarcástico.
What about the 55,000-baht film camera?
¿Y qué hay de la cámara de fotos analógica de 55.000 baht?
Why didn't you give it to him?
¿Por qué no se lo diste?
Huh?
¿Eh?
What kind of camera costs that much?
¿Qué tipo de cámara cuesta tanto?
It's a rare model, you know?
Es un modelo poco común, ¿sabes?
Good on you
Bien por ti
for being able to afford it.
por poder permitírselo.
You're so rich.
Eres tan rico.
If your brother knew about this, he'd scold you until your next life.
Si tu hermano supiera esto, te regañaría hasta tu próxima vida.
I'm not rich.
No soy rico.
I went broke after buying the camera.
Me quedé sin dinero después de comprar la cámara.
When I gave it to him, he refused to accept it.
Cuando se lo di, se negó a aceptarlo.
He told me to sell it. That's why I'm carrying it with me.
Me dijo que lo vendiera. Por eso lo llevo conmigo.
Damn, he's ruthless.
Maldita sea, es despiadado.
He did the right thing.
Hizo lo correcto.
You agree with him?
¿Estás de acuerdo con él?
Why am I in the wrong for doing so much?
¿Por qué estoy equivocado por hacer tanto?
You knew that it was too much.
Sabías que era demasiado.
It's fine. You can overdo something.
No pasa nada. Se puede exagerar con algo.
But if you can't take care of yourself after buying it,
Pero si no puedes cuidarte después de comprarlo,
what good does that make?
¿De qué sirve eso?
Well, I want to give it to him.
Bueno, quiero dárselo a él.
I'm not blaming you for giving him the gift,
No te culpo por haberle dado el regalo,
but it's the fucking price.
pero es el maldito precio.
His mom told me to take care of him.
Su madre me dijo que lo cuidara.
You're talking nonsense at this point.
Estás diciendo tonterías.
Is the point here not letting you take care of Qin?
¿Acaso la cuestión aquí no es dejarte cuidar de Qin?
Why am I not allowed to do this?
¿Por qué no me permiten hacer esto?
You just don't fucking get it.
Simplemente no lo entiendes, joder.
Yeah, I really don't fucking get you.
Sí, la verdad es que no te entiendo.
Damn it, why are you guys fighting?
¡Maldita sea! ¿Por qué están peleando?
I'm not fighting.
No estoy peleando.
Ask yourself what you've done, Duang.
Pregúntate qué has hecho, Duang.
What kind of fucking camera is 55,000 baht?
¿Qué clase de maldita cámara cuesta 55.000 baht?
You're biting off more than you can chew.
Te estás metiendo en un lío del que no puedes salir.
No, why are you being mad at him?
No, ¿por qué estás enfadada con él?
I'm not. I'm just warning him.
No lo soy. Solo le estoy advirtiendo.
Stop being so stupid.
Deja de ser tan estúpido.
You've never been in a relationship; you don't get it, Jamie!
Nunca has tenido una relación; ¡no lo entiendes, Jamie!
Duang!
¡Plan!
Jamie, wait!
¡Jamie, espera!
Damn it.
Maldita sea.
Duang!
¡Plan!
Why the hell did you take it out on him?
¿Por qué demonios te desquitaste con él?
Don't take out your frustration on your friend.
No descargues tu frustración en tu amigo.
Jamie meant well.
Jamie tenía buenas intenciones.
Whenever you want something, he always makes it happen.
Siempre que deseas algo, él siempre lo consigue.
But when he warns you out of goodwill,
Pero cuando te advierte por buena voluntad,
this is how you treat him?
¿Así es como lo tratas?
Fuck.
Mierda.
I'm going to deal with him first.
Voy a ocuparme de él primero.
Qin, can we do another try?
Qin, ¿podemos intentarlo de nuevo?
You made a little bit of a mistake.
Cometiste un pequeño error.
You seem distracted.
Pareces distraído.
Right.
Bien.
One more go, okay?
Una vez más, ¿vale?
What is it, Jamie?
¿Qué pasa, Jamie?
Qin, I'd like to talk about Duang.
Qin, me gustaría hablarte de Duang.
Mm.
Mm.
Thank you for not accepting Duang's expensive gift.
Gracias por no aceptar el costoso regalo de Duang.
Duang's stupid.
Duang es estúpido.
He doesn't listen either.
Él tampoco escucha.
You had a fight with him?
¿Tuviste una pelea con él?
Not exactly.
No exactamente.
The more I talked to him, the more annoyed I became.
Cuanto más hablaba con él, más me irritaba.
That's why I decided to call you instead.
Por eso decidí llamarte.
If you're choosing to be with Cheewin, then go ahead.
Si decides estar con Cheewin, adelante.
I'd rather stay away from
Prefiero mantenerme alejado de
you
tú
and him.
y él.
Get out.
Salir.
What's the deal?
¿Qué pasa?
We're all friends here.
Aquí todos somos amigos.
Are you nuts?
¿Estás loco?
Don't be mad at him.
No te enfades con él.
I'm not exactly mad at him, Qin.
No estoy precisamente enfadado con él, Qin.
But he sees treating someone to expensive stuff as caring.
Pero él considera que regalarle cosas caras a alguien es una muestra de cariño.
I think he needs to be changed.
Creo que necesita cambiar.
He still hasn't sold the camera.
Todavía no ha vendido la cámara.
I think he's probably on his way now.
Creo que probablemente ya esté de camino.
Mm.
Mm.
I'll talk to him.
Hablaré con él.
Right, Qin.
Correcto, Qin.
Come on!
¡Vamos!
You're acting like a child here.
Te estás comportando como un niño.
Well, then...
Bueno, entonces...
Let's take a break for now.
Tomemos un descanso por ahora.
Gosh...
Dios mío...
Finally.
Finalmente.
I'm starving.
Estoy hambriento.
Go have something then, my friend.
Ve a comer algo entonces, amigo mío.
We can't go anywhere.
No podemos ir a ninguna parte.
We'll leave after the practice.
Nos iremos después del entrenamiento.
Are you tired?
¿Estás cansado?
No.
No.
Let's go sell the camera.
Vamos a vender la cámara.
Mm.
Mm.
Let's do that now.
Hagámoslo ahora.
Can you not make that face?
¿Puedes dejar de poner esa cara?
It's like I've done something wrong.
Es como si hubiera hecho algo mal.
No.
No.
What face am I making?
¿Qué cara estoy poniendo?
You can't afford to sell the camera, can you?
No puedes permitirte vender la cámara, ¿verdad?
You're not going to tell me what you're feeling?
¿No me vas a decir lo que sientes?
Well, yes.
Bueno, sí.
I really don't want to sell your first gift.
Realmente no quiero vender tu primer regalo.
Let it all out.
Déjalo salir todo.
Everything I did for you...
Todo lo que hice por ti...
I want you to know that I love you.
Quiero que sepas que te amo.
I want to give you my love as much as I can.
Quiero darte todo mi amor que pueda.
I want you to be happy.
Quiero que seas feliz.
Because you feel sorry for me?
¿Porque sientes lástima por mí?
I heard you talking to my mother.
Te oí hablar con mi madre.
It's true that I feel sorry for you.
Es cierto que siento lástima por ti.
But it's because I love you.
Pero es porque te amo.
I don't want you to feel sorry for me.
No quiero que sientas lástima por mí.
Duang.
Plan.
Can I ask you something?
¿Puedo preguntarte algo?
What is it, Kim?
¿Qué pasa, Kim?
Can you stay away from Qin for now?
¿Puedes mantenerte alejado de Qin por ahora?
He can't focus during practice.
No puede concentrarse durante el entrenamiento.
What do you mean?
¿Qué quieres decir?
I'm doing fine.
Estoy bien.
You're not aware that you can't focus, are you?
No te das cuenta de que no puedes concentrarte, ¿verdad?
It's fine.
Está bien.
I'll be patiently waiting.
Esperaré pacientemente.
I won't disturb you guys during the practice.
No los molestaré durante el entrenamiento.
This showcase is a serious one.
Esta exhibición es muy seria.
It affects our grades, too.
También afecta a nuestras notas.
Mm.
Mm.
I understand.
Entiendo.
That said...
Dicho esto...
I'm heading back.
Me voy.
Good luck.
Buena suerte.
Kim.
Kim.
Why the hell did you say that to Duang?
¿Por qué diablos le dijiste eso a Duang?
Just tell me what's on your mind.
Solo dime qué tienes en mente.
I know that you love each other,
Sé que se aman,
but you have to focus on your part.
pero tienes que concentrarte en tu parte.
I know what I'm doing.
Sé lo que estoy haciendo.
As for the showcase, you need to talk to me,
En cuanto a la presentación, tienes que hablar conmigo,
not Duang.
No Duang.
He distracts you.
Él te distrae.
So we have to tell him too, don't we?
Así que también tenemos que decírselo a él, ¿no?
But it's me who has to take the accountability,
Pero soy yo quien tiene que asumir la responsabilidad,
not him.
Él no.
I didn't blame him, did I?
No le culpé, ¿verdad?
I'm not someone who doesn't take responsibility.
No soy una persona que no asuma responsabilidades.
On top of that,
Además de eso,
I'm one of you guys.
Soy uno de ustedes.
Right, right.
Claro, claro.
I'm sorry.
Lo lamento.
I'm sorry, too.
Yo también lo siento.
Duang and I have some misunderstandings.
Duang y yo tenemos algunos malentendidos.
I'll sort it out soon.
Lo solucionaré pronto.
As for the lack of focus,
En cuanto a la falta de enfoque,
it's on me.
Es mi responsabilidad.
Again, I'm sorry.
De nuevo, lo siento.
Let's do one last practice.
Hagamos un último ejercicio.
Focus on the practice, okay?
Concéntrate en la práctica, ¿de acuerdo?
Then, get everything sorted out later.
Luego, ya lo solucionaremos todo.
What do you think after hearing all of that?
¿Qué opinas después de escuchar todo eso?
Was I being too harsh on my friend?
¿Fui demasiado duro con mi amigo?
You really care about your friend, don't you?
Realmente te preocupas por tu amigo, ¿verdad?
I never knew you had this side.
Nunca supe que tenías este lado.
He's like a brother to me.
Es como un hermano para mí.
It's fun being together with him.
Es divertido estar con él.
Also, being around him is comfortable.
Además, estar cerca de él es agradable.
If you care about him, go talk to him nicely.
Si te importa, ve a hablarle amablemente.
If you want to say sorry, then go ahead.
Si quieres disculparte, adelante.
You suddenly went quiet.
De repente te quedaste en silencio.
I thought you were doing something.
Pensé que estabas haciendo algo.
Can a fashion student like you
¿Puede una estudiante de moda como tú
do this?
¿Hacer esto?
Tell me.
Dime.
I didn't enroll in the class when I had the chance.
No me inscribí en la clase cuando tuve la oportunidad.
It looks complicated.
Parece complicado.
Do you want me to teach you?
¿Quieres que te enseñe?
I'm a pro at this.
Soy un profesional en esto.
Mm.
Mm.
First,
Primero,
make a slip knot.
Haz un nudo corredizo.
Don't say that I'm teaching you...
No digas que te estoy enseñando...
Well, I am.
Bueno, lo soy.
Huh?
¿Eh?
I'm sorry.
Lo lamento.
I was way too much into roleplaying.
Me gustaba demasiado el juego de rol.
I'm getting serious now.
Ahora me lo tomo en serio.
There.
Allá.
What are you making exactly?
¿Qué estás preparando exactamente?
It's a scarf for my mother.
Es una bufanda para mi madre.
There.
Allá.
Rinse and repeat until you're out of yarn.
Enjuaga y repite hasta que se te acabe el hilo.
Push it through,
Empújalo,
loop it over the front,
pásalo por delante,
and pull it back to where it was.
y tirar de él de vuelta a donde estaba.
Then pull it out.
Luego sácalo.
Yes?
¿Sí?
Gosh, took you forever.
¡Dios mío, tardaste una eternidad!
I was cleaning the room.
Estaba limpiando la habitación.
Thought you'd pretend to fall asleep
Pensé que fingirías quedarte dormido.
and ignore my calls.
y no hacen caso a mis llamadas.
Me?
¿A mí?
Get on with it already.
¡Ya es hora de que lo hagan!
I just want to tell you that...
Solo quiero decirte que...
What is it?
¿Qué es?
Say it, Jamie.
Dilo, Jamie.
You're going to apologize to me?
¿Vas a disculparte conmigo?
You know me too well.
Me conoces demasiado bien.
Well...
Bien...
I'm too good.
Soy demasiado bueno.
Right.
Bien.
I'm sorry.
Lo lamento.
I didn't mean to be harsh.
No quise ser duro.
It wasn't my intention.
No era mi intención.
I actually meant well.
En realidad, tenía buenas intenciones.
I'm sorry as well
Yo también lo siento
for being mean to you.
por haber sido malo contigo.
Then that clears things up.
Entonces eso aclara las cosas.
Anything you'd like to tell me?
¿Hay algo que quieras contarme?
I get what you and Qin meant
Entiendo lo que tú y Qin querían decir.
as to why you scolded me.
En cuanto a por qué me regañaste.
Nice, concise, to the point,
Agradable, conciso, directo al grano.
and sharp.
y afilado.
You impressed me, buddy.
Me has impresionado, amigo.
Right.
Bien.
You two have made up, haven't you?
Ustedes dos se han reconciliado, ¿verdad?
Love you, Pae.
Te quiero, Pae.
Gosh. That gave me goosebumps.
Dios mío. Eso me puso la piel de gallina.
I love you, too, Warrior.
Yo también te quiero, guerrero.
Right.
Bien.
Call me if you need anything.
Llámame si necesitas algo.
I'll call you if I do.
Te llamaré si lo hago.
Hey, I'll call you as well.
Oye, yo también te llamaré.
Right.
Bien.
Wow...
Guau...
Why do you love wearing shorts?
¿Por qué te encanta usar pantalones cortos?
It makes me feel things.
Me hace sentir cosas.
They're comfortable.
Son cómodos.
Do you like them?
¿Te gustan?
My legs, do you like them?
¿Te gustan mis piernas?
Nonsense.
Disparates.
You love kissing my legs in bed.
Te encanta besarme las piernas en la cama.
Do you like mine that much, Jamie?
¿Te gusta tanto el mío, Jamie?
Stop it.
Basta.
Teasing you is a lot more fun than cooking.
Burlarse de ti es mucho más divertido que cocinar.
Will we get to have dinner or what?
¿Vamos a cenar o qué?
Why do you love tempting me?
¿Por qué te gusta tentarme?
I'm not tempting you.
I'm not tempting you.
You're the one feeling things.
You're the one feeling things.
I'm weak
I'm weak
to beautiful legs,
to beautiful legs,
especially bright ones. They can make me lose it.
especially bright ones. They can make me lose it.
Did I just turn you on?
Did I just turn you on?
Oh...
Oh...
I guess,
I guess,
I'll get to have you before dinner,
I'll get to have you before dinner,
Marvis.
Marvis.
Hm?
Hm?
No.
No.
I'm not gonna call. I need to hang tough.
I'm not gonna call. I need to hang tough.
I can do this.
I can do this.
I won't call you.
I won't call you.
I won't distract you.
I won't distract you.
Don't do it.
Don't do it.
Hello, where are you?
Hello, where are you?
Uh...
Uh...
Are you done? Do you want me to pick you up?
Are you done? Do you want me to pick you up?
No need.
No need.
I'm at your doorstep.
I'm at your doorstep.
Huh?
Huh?
At my doorstep?
At my doorstep?
Mm.
Mm.
Go inside without me.
Go inside without me.
I'll send you the password in the chat.
I'll send you the password in the chat.
Too cute.
Too cute.
This...
This...
You bought it for 55,000 baht, right?
You bought it for 55,000 baht, right?
If you're not going to sell it,
If you're not going to sell it,
then let it be the gift we bought together.
then let it be the gift we bought together.
How about that?
How about that?
The gift we bought together?
The gift we bought together?
Let me split the bill.
Let me split the bill.
Hey, but...
Hey, but...
I'm accepting the gift you want to give me.
I'm accepting the gift you want to give me.
I simply want to split the bill.
I simply want to split the bill.
Consider this our film camera.
Consider this our film camera.
Can we do that?
Can we do that?
Sure.
Sure.
Yes, we can.
Yes, we can.
Give me the QR code.
Give me the QR code.
I'm paying you.
I'm paying you.
Duang?
Duang?
A gift...
A gift...
It should simply be anything
It should simply be anything
that you want to give.
that you want to give.
It doesn't have to be expensive.
It doesn't have to be expensive.
No need to make up for my family, too.
No need to make up for my family, too.
Remember the first few days you were trying to win my heart?
Remember the first few days you were trying to win my heart?
You made me a box of chocolates.
You made me a box of chocolates.
Do you still remember what kind of emotion was behind that gift?
Do you still remember what kind of emotion was behind that gift?
I gave it because I wanted to.
I gave it because I wanted to.
That's simply enough.
That's simply enough.
That already has a charm to delight the receiver.
That already has a charm to delight the receiver.
I get it now.
I get it now.
I'll capture a whole bunch of our memories with this film camera!
I'll capture a whole bunch of our memories with this film camera!
Mm.
Mm.
By the way,
By the way,
give me your LINE ID.
give me your LINE ID.
It'd be weird not to exchange IDs as a couple, right?
It'd be weird not to exchange IDs as a couple, right?
Here's your boyfriend's LINE ID.
Here's your boyfriend's LINE ID.
Added.
Added.
Oh.
Oh.
How did you know I'm staying here?
How did you know I'm staying here?
How did you know where my place is?
How did you know where my place is?
Well...
Well...
Hello, Jamie.
Hello, Jamie.
Are you with Duang?
Are you with Duang?
I'm not with him, Qin.
I'm not with him, Qin.
How about looking for him at his place?
How about looking for him at his place?
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry.
I got us boiled chicken and rice.
I got us boiled chicken and rice.
Let me get it plated for us.
Let me get it plated for us.
I'm really happy that you came to my place.
I'm really happy that you came to my place.
My room without you is just...
My room without you is just...
It feels weird.
It feels weird.
Why?
Why?
So you're hooked on me now?
So you're hooked on me now?
Mm.
Mm.
Qin?!
Qin?!
You didn't answer my calls.
You didn't answer my calls.
You didn't call me back either.
You didn't call me back either.
- You called me? - Take a look.
- You called me? - Take a look.
What?!
What?!
You did call me!
You did call me!
You must have called me when I was getting changed.
You must have called me when I was getting changed.
I was going to text you when I got here,
I was going to text you when I got here,
but I worried I'd distract you.
but I worried I'd distract you.
Kim said...
Kim said...
The jazz showcase is
The jazz showcase is
very important to you guys.
very important to you guys.
It was my fault for not being able to concentrate during practice.
It was my fault for not being able to concentrate during practice.
I was worried about my boyfriend.
I was worried about my boyfriend.
I didn't think much of it.
I didn't think much of it.
Liar.
Liar.
Well, I kind of did.
Well, I kind of did.
I really love you,
I really love you,
and I don't want to cause you problems.
and I don't want to cause you problems.
You aren't the only one in love here.
No eres el único enamorado aquí.
I love you, too.
Yo también te amo.
(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
(Ver en www.kisskh.xyz Administrador de soporte)
Also...
También...
Can you not just disappear without warning?
¿No puedes simplemente desaparecer sin previo aviso?
I'm not used to it,
No estoy acostumbrado a eso,
not seeing new messages
No veo mensajes nuevos
from you on Instagram.
De ti en Instagram.
Sure thing.
Claro que sí.
I won't simply disappear.
No voy a desaparecer sin más.
You now know that
Ahora ya sabes que
I love only you, right?
Solo te amo a ti, ¿verdad?
I love you very much.
Te quiero muchísimo.
I do.
Sí.
Even the password...
Incluso la contraseña...
Oops.
Ups.
It's my birth date.
Es mi fecha de nacimiento.
When I knew what your birth date was,
Cuando supe cuál era tu fecha de nacimiento,
I got excited and set it as the password.
Me emocioné y la puse como contraseña.
When are you going to dig in?
¿Cuándo vas a empezar a comer?
I'm hungry now.
Ahora tengo hambre.
Let's.
Vamos.
You have no clue
No tienes ni idea
how many things about you I've looked up,
cuántas cosas sobre ti he buscado,
like what you like and dislike.
Te gusta lo que te gusta y lo que no.
Why wouldn't I know?
¿Por qué no lo sabría?
I scolded you for it. Can't you remember?
Te regañé por eso. ¿No te acuerdas?
What the fuck are you looking at?
¿Qué coño estás mirando?
Yeah, you're right.
Sí, tienes razón.
This time, it comes with your voice.
Esta vez, viene con tu voz.
You want more?
¿Quieres más?
I can let you scold me all day.
Puedo dejar que me regañes todo el día.
What the fuck are you looking at?
¿Qué coño estás mirando?
Any snacks in the fridge?
¿Hay algún aperitivo en la nevera?
I don't think so, but I'll check it.
No lo creo, pero lo comprobaré.
No, I'll do it.
No, lo haré yo.
There are cans of beer. Want one?
Hay latas de cerveza. ¿Quieres una?
I do.
Sí.
I'm drinking it outdoors.
La estoy bebiendo al aire libre.
It hits better.
Se siente mejor.
Follow me when you're done.
Sígueme cuando hayas terminado.
Better watch it, though.
Será mejor que lo veas.
I'll devour you the minute you get drunk.
Te devoraré en cuanto te emborraches.
You're the one who needs to watch it.
Eres tú quien tiene que verlo.
What do you mean?
¿Qué quieres decir?
You're going to devour me?
¿Vas a devorarme?
Aww...
Oooh...
I'll allow it.
Lo permitiré.
Ridiculous.
Ridículo.
It reminds me of you,
Me recuerda a ti,
so I got it for you.
Así que lo conseguí para ti.
Aww...
Oooh...
It's so sweet.
Es tan dulce.
Thank you.
Gracias.
My heart's pounding right now.
Mi corazón late con fuerza ahora mismo.
This already makes me happy.
Esto ya me hace feliz.
By the way...
Por cierto...
Why does this doggo remind you of me?
¿Por qué este perrito te recuerda a mí?
Well...
Bien...
You're always my protector.
Siempre eres mi protector.
So I want this little guy to protect you on my behalf.
Así que quiero que este pequeño te proteja en mi nombre.
I thought you'd say I looked like a dog.
Pensé que dirías que parecía un perro.
Whose guitar is that?
¿De quién es esa guitarra?
It's Funan's.
Es de Funan.
I can't play it, actually.
En realidad, no puedo jugarlo.
I can't play any instruments.
No sé tocar ningún instrumento.
But you can play all sorts of instruments, no?
Pero puedes tocar todo tipo de instrumentos, ¿no?
Whoa...
Vaya...
You already look very cool posing!
¡Ya te ves genial posando!
Can I make you some noise?
¿Puedo hacerte algo de ruido?
Stop playing around already.
Deja de bromear ya.
♫Some day, I might walk through time,♫
♫Algún día, tal vez camine a través del tiempo,♫
♫Where our ticking clocks are aligned♫
♫Donde nuestros relojes marcan el tiempo♫
♫And when time brings us together,♫
♫Y cuando el tiempo nos reúne,♫
♫I'll hold you forever,♫
♫Te abrazaré para siempre,♫
♫The one I've been waiting for♫
♫El que he estado esperando♫
Right.
Bien.
When I was at your house,
Cuando estuve en tu casa,
I saw a massive piano.
Vi un piano enorme.
Other instruments you can play?
¿Sabes tocar otros instrumentos?
Can you play the violin?
¿Sabes tocar el violín?
Kind of.
Un poco.
"Kind of" means you're a pro at it, I'm sure.
"Más o menos" significa que eres un experto en ello, estoy seguro.
Even your mom says that you're talented.
Incluso tu madre dice que tienes talento.
Mm...
Mm...
That reminds me.
Eso me recuerda.
I tried to be as polite as I could,
Traté de ser lo más educado posible,
but I was too chatty, right?
Pero yo era demasiado habladora, ¿verdad?
Fortunately,
Afortunadamente,
at least we became boyfriends at your house,
al menos nos hicimos novios en tu casa,
creating new memories there on top of that.
Además, creamos nuevos recuerdos allí .
Did I say something wrong?
¿Dije algo malo?
This is my bedroom.
Este es mi dormitorio.
Actually,
De hecho,
I've never told anyone about this.
Nunca le he contado esto a nadie.
But I want to tell you now.
Pero quiero decírtelo ahora.
I'm always quiet,
Siempre estoy callado,
and I refuse to talk to anyone I'm not close to.
y me niego a hablar con nadie con quien no tenga una relación cercana.
There's a reason behind it.
Hay una razón detrás de ello.
I get it.
Lo entiendo.
You're an introvert. I know that.
Eres introvertido. Lo sé.
No need to hide it.
No hay necesidad de ocultarlo.
You heard it from my mother, didn't you?
Lo oíste de mi madre, ¿verdad?
I was just an ordinary child.
Yo era solo un niño normal y corriente.
I talked like others.
Hablé como los demás.
I was just as curious
Yo también tenía curiosidad.
as other kids.
como los demás niños.
The only person I could ask anything of
La única persona a la que podría pedirle algo
was my babysitter.
era mi niñera.
My parents weren't there for me.
Mis padres no estuvieron ahí para mí.
What is this called?
¿Cómo se llama esto?
An elephant.
Un elefante.
Don't know what it is?
¿No sabes qué es?
What about this one in Thai?
¿Qué tal esta en tailandés?
"Ma."
"Y."
Are you stupid?
¿Eres estúpido?
You don't know what a horse in Thai is?
¿No sabes qué es un caballo en tailandés?
- Why does it sound like "mama"? - Gosh!
- ¿Por qué suena como "mamá"? - ¡Caramba!
Can you just shut up?
¿Puedes callarte ya?
Stop asking me questions! So annoying!
¡Deja de hacerme preguntas! ¡Qué molesto!
- But... - Gosh!!
- Pero... - ¡Dios mío!
Are you crying?
¿Estás llorando?
Why are you crying?!
¿Por qué lloras?
Why the hell are you crying?!
¿Por qué diablos estás llorando?
Gosh!
¡Dios mío!
So annoying!
¡Qué molesto!
Stop crying already!
¡Deja de llorar ya!
I told you to fucking stop crying!
¡Te dije que dejaras de llorar, maldita sea!
You're not going to stop?
¿No vas a parar?
If you keep crying,
Si sigues llorando,
I'll throw you out of the house so that you can cry all day.
Te echaré de casa para que llores todo el día.
Stop it already!
¡Basta ya!
You want to cry, right?!
¡Tienes ganas de llorar, ¿verdad?!
Then go ahead!
¡Entonces adelante!
Cry all you want!
¡Llora todo lo que quieras!
Cry here, outside the house.
Llora aquí, fuera de la casa.
Are you going to stop?!
¿Vas a parar?
You're not going to stop?
¿No vas a parar?
Fine!
¡Bien!
Papa, mama...
Papá, mamá...
Are you going to stop?
¿Vas a parar?
Are you going to shut up?!
¿Te vas a callar?
If you won't stop, I'll shove mud inside your mouth.
Si no paras, te voy a meter barro en la boca.
Are you going to stop?!
¿Vas a parar?
Qin.
Qin.
I have to go to dinner outside tonight.
Tengo que ir a cenar fuera esta noche.
Would you like to come with me?
¿Te gustaría venir conmigo?
No?
¿No?
You want to stay here and play all by yourself?
¿Quieres quedarte aquí y jugar tú solo?
Well then, stay inside with Sorn, okay?
Bueno, entonces quédate dentro con Sorn, ¿de acuerdo?
Please take care of Qin, Sorn.
Por favor, cuida de Qin, Sorn.
What a relief.
Qué alivio.
Since having you here, I've been feeling a lot more comfortable.
Desde que estás aquí, me siento mucho más a gusto.
Stay with us for years to come, okay?
Quédate con nosotros durante los próximos años, ¿de acuerdo?
Yes.
Sí.
Don't worry.
No te preocupes.
I'll take good care of Qin.
Cuidaré bien de Qin.
I'll leave him to you.
Te lo dejo a ti.
Understood.
Comprendido.
I'll be going now.
Me voy ahora.
Say anything,
Di algo,
and I'll make you eat mud.
y te haré comer barro.
I couldn't do anything.
No pude hacer nada.
I wanted to ask for help,
Quería pedir ayuda,
and every time I called for my parents,
y cada vez que llamaba a mis padres,
they were never there.
Nunca estuvieron allí.
They had no idea who I really was
No tenían ni idea de quién era yo realmente.
or what I'd been through.
o lo que yo había vivido.
They knew that I wasn't normal.
Sabían que yo no era normal.
They took me to a psychiatrist.
Me llevaron a un psiquiatra.
Qin.
Qin.
Did you say hello to him?
¿Le dijiste hola?
Hello.
Hola.
My name is Kao.
Mi nombre es Kao.
What's your name?
¿Cómo te llamas?
So...
Entonces...
He rarely talks to anyone but his parents.
Rara vez habla con alguien que no sean sus padres.
He's a quiet boy.
Es un chico tranquilo.
He's not sociable.
No es sociable.
If that's the case, can I ask you a question?
Si ese es el caso, ¿puedo hacerle una pregunta?
Is there anything you'd like to tell me?
¿Hay algo que quieras contarme?
If that's the case...
Si ese es el caso...
Can I examine the area under your clothes?
¿Puedo examinar la zona que hay debajo de tu ropa?
Under his clothes?
¿Debajo de su ropa?
Yes.
Sí.
Qin...
Qin...
May I take a look, son?
¿Puedo echar un vistazo, hijo?
Honey...
Miel...
Oh? What's this?
¿Oh? ¿Qué es esto?
Qin?
¿Qin?
Oh...
Oh...
What happened to you?
¿Lo que le pasó?
Honey...
Miel...
Check the security cameras.
Revisa las cámaras de seguridad.
Oh, dear...
Oh querido...
Look at this...
Mira esto...
You want to cry, right?!
¡Tienes ganas de llorar, ¿verdad?!
Cry all you want!
¡Llora todo lo que quieras!
Go ahead!
¡Adelante!
Cry here, outside the house.
Llora aquí, fuera de la casa.
Coming home already?
¿Ya vuelves a casa?
Qin.
Qin.
Go and wait for me upstairs, okay?
Ve a esperarme arriba, ¿de acuerdo?
What does this mean?
¿Qué quiere decir esto?
But there shouldn't be any cameras there...
Pero no debería haber cámaras allí...
Why did you do that?!
¿Por qué hiciste eso?
I... I didn't mean to.
Yo... yo no quise hacerlo.
Pack up your belongings
Empaca tus pertenencias
and get out of my house.
y lárgate de mi casa.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Lo siento. Lo siento mucho.
I'm so sorry.
Lo siento mucho.
I didn't mean to do it.
No fue mi intención hacerlo.
Go and get your stuff
Ve y recoge tus cosas
before I call the police.
antes de llamar a la policía.
He's an insufferable brat.
Es un mocoso insoportable.
He never listens to what I say. What the hell was I supposed to do?
Nunca escucha lo que le digo. ¿Qué demonios se suponía que debía hacer?
If you cared that much about him,
Si tanto te importaba,
then take care of him yourselves!
¡Entonces cuídenlo ustedes mismos!
Do you want to know something?
¿Quieres saber algo?
Even a dog knows how to be grateful when you feed it,
Incluso un perro sabe agradecer cuando le das de comer.
unlike you.
a diferencia de ti.
Want to know something?
¿Quieres saber algo?
Even a dog loves its pups,
Incluso un perro ama a sus cachorros,
unlike you two.
a diferencia de ustedes dos.
Hiring you to take care of our son
Te contratamos para que cuides de nuestro hijo.
doesn't mean that we don't love him.
Eso no significa que no lo queramos.
We make a living
Nos ganamos la vida
to pay for his tuition.
para pagar su matrícula.
When he grows up, I'm going to teach him
Cuando crezca, le voy a enseñar.
how to be grateful to others,
cómo ser agradecido con los demás,
the quality you lack.
la cualidad que te falta.
Your parents must not have taught you what it is.
Tus padres no deben haberte enseñado qué es.
Don't fucking preach to me!
¡No me des sermones, maldita sea!
I hope you have time to fucking teach him.
Espero que tengas tiempo para enseñarle una maldita cosa.
You have money, social status, and everything,
Tienes dinero, estatus social y todo lo demás.
yet you can't spare the time for your son.
Sin embargo, no puedes dedicarle tiempo a tu hijo.
He must've really loved you guys!
¡Debió de quererlos mucho!
Keep treating him like this,
Sigue tratándolo así,
and your son will end up a problematic child.
y tu hijo acabará siendo un niño problemático.
Education is important.
La educación es importante.
Good!
¡Bien!
Good. Have him study hard
Bien. Que estudie mucho.
so that he'll get to meet other people.
para que pueda conocer a otras personas.
After classes,
Después de clases,
he'll get to meet friends who have good parents.
Tendrá la oportunidad de conocer amigos que tienen buenos padres.
Parents who wait at school to take them home.
Padres que esperan en la escuela para llevarlos a casa.
He'll be the only one
Él será el único
who gets taken care of and driven around by a babysitter and driver.
quien es atendido y llevado de un lado a otro por una niñera y un chófer.
Oh?!
¡¿Oh?!
Here's the kicker.
Aquí viene lo mejor.
He won't get to meet his parents when he gets home!
¡No podrá conocer a sus padres cuando vuelva a casa!
Gosh, what a happy family!
¡Caramba, qué familia tan feliz!
It's as if he were an orphan!
¡Es como si fuera huérfano!
I'm curious.
Tengo curiosidad.
What will he be like when he grows up?
¿Cómo será cuando crezca?
Are you done babbling?
¿Ya terminaste de parlotear?
If you are, then get out.
Si lo eres, entonces vete.
No need to tell me!
¡No hace falta que me lo digas!
I'm leaving for sure!
¡Me voy seguro!
I'm saying these because I want your son to hear it, too!
¡Digo esto porque quiero que tu hijo también lo escuche!
Even when I'm gone,
Incluso cuando me haya ido,
you won't get to be with your damn parents!
¡No podrás estar con tus malditos padres!
That's enough.
Ya es suficiente.
Let's leave.
Vámonos.
Where are you going, Miss?
¿Adónde va, señorita?
I'm not done here.
Todavía no he terminado.
You can't stand these words already?
¿Ya no soportas estas palabras?
I told you to get out of my house.
Te dije que te fueras de mi casa.
- Get out! - What I wanted was
- ¡Fuera! - Lo que yo quería era
a hug from my parents.
Un abrazo de mis padres.
I wanted them to be with me,
Quería que estuvieran conmigo,
to give me warmth, like a family would.
para darme calor, como lo haría una familia.
I never got any of that.
Nunca entendí nada de eso.
They fired the babysitter,
Despidieron a la niñera,
and pretended like nothing ever happened.
y fingió que no había pasado nada.
They never once hugged me.
Nunca me abrazaron.
How about this?
¿Qué te parece esto?
I don't know if it'd work for you,
No sé si te funcionaría.
but if your past memories
pero si tus recuerdos del pasado
hurt you,
Te lastimé,
it's time to let go of your younger self's hands
Es hora de soltar las manos de tu yo más joven.
and hold mine.
y sujeta la mía.
I'll take it from here.
Yo me encargo a partir de ahora.
I was just an ordinary child.
Yo era solo un niño normal y corriente.
I talked like others.
Hablé como los demás.
What I wanted was
Lo que quería era
a hug from my parents.
Un abrazo de mis padres.
Why the hell are you crying?!
¿Por qué diablos estás llorando?
I only want the best for him.
Solo quiero lo mejor para él.
Stop crying already!
¡Deja de llorar ya!
That hurt like hell back then, you know?
Eso dolió muchísimo en aquel entonces, ¿sabes?
You can now explain how you feel?
¿Ya puedes explicar cómo te sientes?
- I wish to cry like others, but couldn't. - Try crying one more time.
- Quisiera llorar como los demás, pero no pude. - Intenta llorar una vez más.
Gosh, what a happy family!
¡Caramba, qué familia tan feliz!
It's as if he were an orphan!
¡Es como si fuera huérfano!
- He rarely talks to anyone but his parents. - You said nothing back then.
- Casi nunca habla con nadie que no sean sus padres. - No dijiste nada entonces.
- Mama, papa... - I told you to shut up!
- Mamá, papá... - ¡Les dije que se callaran!
I thought...
Pensé...
Qin wouldn't probably remember those things.
Qin probablemente no recordaría esas cosas.
It's time to let go of your younger self's hands.
Es hora de soltar las riendas de tu yo más joven.
Why are you crying?!
¿Por qué lloras?
Best of luck with everything moving forward.
Te deseo mucha suerte en todo lo que venga después.
I promise you...
Te prometo que...
I'll always be right by your side.
Siempre estaré a tu lado.
I'll be everything for you.
Seré todo para ti.
Walk with me, Qin.
Camina conmigo, Qin.
Don't cry, okay.
No llores, ¿de acuerdo?
Mom and Dad love you;
Mamá y papá te aman;
otherwise, they wouldn't have come back so quickly.
De lo contrario, no habrían regresado tan rápido.
You said you wanted us to be with you.
Dijiste que querías que estuviéramos contigo.
Is everything okay?
¿Está todo bien?
Thank you, Duang,
Gracias, Duang.
for always sticking by my side.
Por estar siempre a mi lado.
Do you think people outside will know
¿Crees que la gente de fuera lo sabrá?
I'm teasing you?
¿Te estoy tomando el pelo?
I want to invite you over for a meal.
Me gustaría invitarte a comer a mi casa.
- I'm back!! - Calm down.
- ¡He vuelto! - Cálmate.
This is my boyfriend.
Este es mi novio.
He is...
Él es...
Taking a shower together
Tomar una ducha juntos
helps save the environment.
ayuda a salvar el medio ambiente.
♫Have no fear, I'm by your side♫
♫No temas, estoy a tu lado♫
♫Let me be the one loving you♫
♫Déjame ser quien te ame♫
♫My heart aches for you through and through♫
♫Mi corazón te anhela profundamente♫
♫From now on, my words of love end with you♫
♫A partir de ahora, mis palabras de amor terminan contigo♫
♫I'm prepared to love you with all my soul♫
♫Estoy preparado para amarte con toda mi alma♫
♫My being will be yours as a whole♫
♫Mi ser será tuyo en su totalidad♫
♫Whatever tomorrow lies,♫
♫Sea cual sea el mañana,♫
♫Have no fear, I'm by your side♫
♫No temas, estoy a tu lado♫
♫Let me be the one loving you♫
♫Déjame ser quien te ame♫
♫My heart aches for you through and through♫
♫Mi corazón te anhela profundamente♫
♫From now on, my words of love only end with you♫
♫De ahora en adelante, mis palabras de amor solo terminan contigo♫
[Duang With You]
[Duang contigo]